platypusplatypus.com 2019-06-30

# Privacy | Platypus Platypus

Privacy Policy

Your use of the site and Services is your agreement to abide by this policy and the Terms of Use. By accessing the site and Services, you agree that you have read and abide by both documents. Please read both carefully.  
Your Privacy

I. Data  
The following is data we gather from you in order to improve our services and your experience:  
Non-Personally Identifiable Information: We collect and use information about your interactions with the Service in a manner and format that does not identify you as an individual (“NPII”). We may collect, use, and disclose the following types of Non-Personally Identifiable Information:

Analytics: We use third-party analytics tools to help us measure traffic and usage trends for the Service. These tools collect information sent by your browser as part of a web page request, including the web pages you visit, your browser add-ons, your browser’s width and height, and other information that assists us in improving the Service.

Cookies: Our site sends and uses cookies to gather data on actions you take on our site and other information.  
II. Sharing  
We may share your information with other third parties, such as advertisers or sponsors.

III. Your Information  
We store and process your information on data centers located within the US. We may transfer your information to other jurisdictions around the world. Note that other countries may have different laws regarding privacy. We use commercially available methods to safeguard your information, though we cannot guarantee that your infomation may not be accessed by an illegal act.

IV. Children  
We do not knowingly collect or solicit Personally Identifiable Information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register as Users. The Service and its content are not directed at children under the age of 13. If you are under 13, please do not send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible.  
Contact  
You may contact us with any questions at hey@platypusplatypus.com

Changes  
This may be changed with or without notice. Your use of the site is your consent to abide by this policy.

Updates  
This was last updated 12/25/15.
